# Lim Say Juan

Address: Blk 349 Clementi Ave #05-03 120349 Singapore, Singapore Phone number: +65 8874 8200

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/lim-say-juan-569438269

# **Summary Statement**

Please call me "Mr. Full Stack" OR "Mr. Blockchain". I am a hardworking and detail oriented full-stack web architect with 9 years of experience. I am as comfortable working with both startups and enterprise solutions and focus on directed growth, technical solutions to reduce bottlenecks and creative strategy.

# **Work Experience**

#### SENIOR FULL-STACK ENGINEER AT EATCLUB

Victoria, Australia (September 2021 – December 2022) https://eatclub.com.au/

- · Helped organize and develop flexible access patterns for complex data sets to map to **GraphQL**.
- · Developed a lifestyle and calorie counting application using native iOS programming.
- · Integrated with **Salesforce** via **API** for clients to maintain data consistency with their internal teams.
- Created a Node.js parallel processing add-on to analyze statistical data from chats for further AI input data.
  Developed binary protocols for data processing and transportation.
- · Developed and implemented a strategy for migrating the **front-end** codebase to **React** additively.
- Developed a unique contact book using native iOS programming with effective synchronization over multiple platforms.

### **BLOCKCHAIN ENGINEER AT RUBIX**

Victoria, Australia (October 2019 — July 2021) https://rubix.com.au/

- · Worked on the block difficulty adjustment algorithm for the blockchain in Golang.
- Optimized application in **Golang** for thread contention. Optimized incoming channel distribution with a specific algorithm and maintained data integrity across the application.
- Fixed data corruption by fixing thread safety issues and optimized runtime operations around signature generation.
- · Refactored the core blockchain to allow **higher transactions** per second.

### MOBILE APP DEVELOPER AT SOCASH

Singapore, Singapore (May 2018 — September 2019) https://www.socash.io/

- Refactored around 80% of the code and set up coding standards while migrating the project to Android Studio and Gradle.
- Developed new and added to the existing features, mainly in-app purchases, tablet redesign, drag-n-drop support, and more app specifics using Flutter.
- · Made the **crash rate lower** than in the **iOS** version, first in the application's history.
- Created the back-end's structure and underlying API calls using a Firebase database and Firebase Functions.

#### SENIOR FRONTEND ENGINEER AT GLADLY

Singapore, Singapore (June 2017 – April 2018) https://www.gladly.com/

- · Maintained code for the insurance solution using **Node**, **React**, and **MongoDB**.
- Delivered **100% bug-free** solutions for a **REST API** module that consumes data from internal and external web services and produces information in **JSON** format aimed at our **React** web app.
- · Helped the **QA** team finish their testing plan for some of the released versions of the system.
- Converted the starting Node/React project into a production-ready solution using **Docker**, **Heroku**, and **AWS**.

## **JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER AT SHIOKMEATS**

Singapore, Singapore (November 2015 - May 2017) https://shiokmeats.com/

- · Created an internal tool for randomly assigning seats to employees in the office on a weekly basis.
- · Developed a runtime engine which compiles and runs coding custom tasks using **Node.js** and **Docker**.
- · Built and maintained development, staging, and production infrastructure on AWS.
- · Created a **Node.js** parallel processing add-on to analyze statistical data from chats for further **AI** input data. Developed binary protocols for data processing and transportation.

#### SOFTWARE INTERN AT WILLOWMORE IOT

Singapore, Singapore (October 2014 – October 2015) https://www.willowmore.com.sg/

- Developed features for the back-end in **Java** with **Servlet** functionality to increase target audience engagement by 14%.
- Took 6 months academic course about provided support for an **ERP** system, and their impacts on application concurrency.
- · Made the API endpoints using JSON Schemas to model and validate the input and output.

## **Education**

## **BACHELOR OF SCIENCE (B.S.)**

National University of Singapore

April 2010- May 2014

Computer and Information Faculty

## **Skills & Abilities**

- · Go, Rust, Node.js, Django, Python, Laravel, Spring, GraphQL
- · React, Angular, Vue, Next.js, Nuxt.js, Web3.js, Flutter, React Native
- · HTML/CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, MUI
- · AWS, GCP, Firebase, Azure
- · PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Elasticsearch, Redis
- · Git

## Languages

**English: Fluent Proficiency**